先生们 我告诉你们哟
Gentlemen,I put it to you:
最难吃西米布丁也好过其他口味优质布丁
the worst tapioca pudding is better than the best pudding of any other flavor.
首先 明眼人都知道这话错的 因为最好的布丁是巧克力口味
First off,that is axiomatically wrong because the best pudding is chocolate.
其次 西米的有机结构使布丁 黏糊糊摇晃晃 有潜在致命危险
Secondly,the organic structure of tapioca makes it a jiggling bowl of potential death.
是从植物里提取...
It is extracted from the plant...
嘿 我在考虑留点胡子
Hey,I'm thinking of growing a mustache.
不是吧?
No kidding?
傅满洲那样的? 八字胡 又尖又长?
Fu Manchu,a handlebar,pencil?
- 是从植物中提取 - 还没想好呢
- It's extracted from the plant. - I'm not sure yet.
乔治·克鲁尼现在也留胡子呢
You know,George Clooney has one now.
真的? 我看到过他在拉夫斯超市买龙舌兰酒
Really? I once saw him shopping at Ralph's. He was buying tequila.
你以为他们会有仆人跑腿买酒吗?
You'd think a guy like that would have some kind of booze lackey.
好啦 太残忍了
All right,this is cruel.
我们还是让他说完 不然人家要爆头了
We'd better let him finish before his head explodes.
好吧 谢尔顿 为啥西...
All right,Sheldon,why is tap...
西米由食用木薯根茎提取而成
Tapioca is extracted from the root of the plant manihot esculenta!
由于富含高浓度的氰化物
Due to a high concentration of cyanide,
其本身有毒性 如加工不当即食用会致命
it is poisonous in its raw form and lethal if prepared improperly!
现在爽了吧?
Feel better now?
同时可可豆也是巴西的 从中能提取巧克力 做最好的布丁
It is also indigenous to Brazil as is the coa bean,from which we get chocolate,the best pudding.
求你们别再耍我了!
And you promised you wouldn't do that anymore!
嘿 霍夫施塔特
Hey,Hofstadter.
嘿 Kripke
Hey,Kripke.
听说你最新的反质子衰变实验了
Heard about your latest anti-proton decay experiment.
收集两万数据 却没啥有用的结果
20,000 data runs and no statistically significant results.
灰常了得
Very impressive.
蠢货一个
What a jerk.
别气馁 莱纳德 没用的结果也是结果
Don't feel bad,Leonard. Negative results are still results.
- 就算两万又算啥 - 行啦!
- Even 20,000 of them. - All right!
求你们别在给我打气了
Please don't cheer me up anymore.
别呀 不要让他打击到你 Kripke哪根葱
Come on. Don't let him get to you. It's Kripke.
对呀 大蠢蛋一个
Yeah,he's a ginormous knob.
所以他孤单用餐 而不能坐到这酷酷的桌子来
That's why he eats by himself instead of sitting here at the cool table.
说得对呀
For shizzle.
确实啊 Kripke确实缺乏 咱固有的那种基本社交技巧
It's true Kripke lacks the basic social skills that we take for granted.
但他还操控着新的开放科学网格计算机
But he also controls the new open science grid computer
而我需要它来模拟宇宙早期的结构形态
that I need to use to run some simulations of structure formation in the early universe.
看你有没有那命用上吧
Well,good luck getting time on it.
他可只让他的朋友使用
The only people he lets use it are his friends.
那 解决办法很简单嘛
Well,then,the solution is simple.
我去和他做朋友
I shall befriend him.
Kripke!
啥事?
Yeah?
你觉得我们交个朋友如何?
What would you say to the idea of you and I becoming friends?
我觉得木有啥兴趣哟
I would say I have no interest in becoming your friend.
当真?
Really?
你个里里外外不受欢迎的家伙 目光还真是相当短浅呀
That seems rather shortsighted coming from someone who is generally considered altogether unlikable.
不如重新考虑下吧?
Why don't you take some time to reconsider?
行呀 我去想想
Yeah,I'll do that.
看来咱这开局不错啊
Well,I think we're off to a terrific start.
《生活大爆炸》
第二季  第13集
好了
There you go.
现在所有沃尔伍兹发来的邮件 都会直接进入垃圾箱
Now any e-mail from Wolowitz will go right into your spam folder.
多谢 其实骚扰邮件倒没啥 他穿浴衣的度假照比较雷人
Thanks. I mean,the e-mail doesn't bother me as much as the vacation pictures of him in a bathing suit.
是呀 我也收到了 那可不是浴衣 是晒痕
Yeah,I got the same one,and that's not a bathing suit. It's a tan line.
你好 我是谢尔顿·库珀
Hello,this is Sheldon Cooper.
这是给贝瑞·克里帕奇的留言
I am leaving a message for Barry Kripke.
贝瑞 很高兴在食堂与你邂逅
Barry,it was pleasant seeing you today in the cafeteria.
我注意到你买了推荐沙拉
I saw that you purchased the chef's salad.
显然 你不知道推荐沙拉是 食堂的杂碎肉骗人把戏
Apparently,you did not know that the chef's salad is kitchen trickery to utilize scrap meat.
不过呢 我希望你用餐愉快
Nevertheless,I hope you enjoyed it.
我在追踪待定友谊的发展状况 期待你来电给它定位哟
I'm following up on our pending friendship and I look forward to hearing from you regarding its status.
我是谢尔顿·库珀
Sheldon Cooper.
胆小发明家又咋了?
What's up with Ichabod?
他在交友呢
Uh,he's trying to make a new friend.
真的? 不错嘛
Oh,really? Well,good for him.
除非他像杰佩托做出皮诺曹 不然没戏的
Well,unless he makes one out of wood like Geppetto,I don't think it's gonna happen.
那你们咋成为朋友的?
How did you guys become friends?
大学公告板上的一张传单
There was a flyer on the bulletin board at the university:
"招募室友 吹口哨的勿扰"
"Roommate wanted.Whistlers need not apply."
你就搬进去了?
And you moved in anyway?
我以为他说着玩的
I assumed he was joking.
你绝对想不到有多少量子物理学家 都有反复无常的一面
You'd be surprised how many particle physicists have a whimsical side.
霍华德和拉吉呢? 我是说他咋和他们好上的?
What about Howard and Raj? I mean,how did he become friends with them?
不知道 碳原子是如何构成苯环的?
I don't know. How do carbon atoms form a benzene ring?
价电子亲近
Proximity and valence electrons.
是呀 你这样说也是哈
Well,sure,when you put it that way.
但相处的也不错是吧
But it all worked out,right?
差不多吧 尽管我很怀念口哨
I suppose. I do miss whistling,though.
不是吧?
Oh,come on. Really?
警告一次
First warning.
佩妮 佩妮 佩妮
Penny? Penny? Penny?
给你的
This is for you.
你好 谢尔顿
Hello,Sheldon.
这是啥?
What is this?
我设计的调查表
It's a questionnaire I devised.
我和一位同事交友遇到点困难
I'm having some difficulty bonding with a colleague at work
所以我想做些小调查 更好的了解 为什么我目前的朋友们喜欢我
so I'm doing a little research to better understand why my current friends like me.
嗯 这个问题值得考虑
Yes,well,that is a good question.
但你确定这是最好的办法了?
But is this really the best way to figure it out?
问得好 社会学家很大程度是忽悠
I agree. The social sciences are largely hokum.
但又不能插一个电极到你的大脑 探测你对我友谊问题的反应
But short of putting electrodes in your brain and monitoring your response to my companionship,
就这方法还凑合了
this is the best I can do.
好 "问题1: 按吸引力程度给 谢尔顿·库珀以下各方面排序
Okay,"Question one: "Rank the following aspects of Sheldon Cooper "in order of appeal:"
聪明 洁癖 有趣 Java程序编写?"
Intelligence;ruthless attention to hygiene;playfulness; JAVA applet writing"?
也许头一个问题答案过分明显
I know,I may have started out with a fairly obvious one;
谁不知道我最吸引人的特质之一 有趣
an aspect of my most appealing trait: playfulness.
你直接把它排到1号吧
Why don't you just go ahead and rank that number one?
恐怕剩下的我不能指导你了
I'm afraid you're on your own for the rest.
用不了三个小时就可以完成
It should take you no more than three hours.
等下 这玩意儿有多少个问题呀?
Well,wait. How many questions are on this thing?
区区211个
Only 211.
别担心 为了照顾你 这份高中毕业就能读懂
Don't worry. In deference to you,I kept them all at a high school graduate reading level.
还得谢你 哥们儿
Thanks,pal.
客气啥...姐们儿
You got it... buddy.
谢尔顿 亲爱的 你有没有考虑过 通过让人开心来交友啊?
Sheldon,honey,did you ever consider making friends by being,I don't know,pleasant?
那当然是一个发人深思的假设
Well,that's certainly a thought-provoking hypothesis.
我看你论文写这题目好了
May I suggest it as the topic for your essay?
你的调查问卷 十分让人失望呀
Your questionnaire,very disappointing.
我逢题必答呀 谢尔顿
I answered every question,Sheldon.
你选择题很有规律嘛
You answered the multiple choice questions in a pattern:
A B B A C A B B A C
A- B-A-C.A- B-A-C.
你发现了哈
Oh,you picked up on that,huh?
我怎么会发现不了?
How could I not?
行行好 超过200个问题
Come on. There's over 200 questions.
看有些问题吧
And look at some of these things.
"谢尔顿之于友谊如同太空梭之于什么?"
"Sheldon is to camaraderie as the space shuttle is to blank?"
这里有些适合的答案呀
There are a number of acceptable answers.
例如 C近地运输机
For example,Near-Earth transport."
但绝对不是B鳄梨种植工
But certainly not Avocado rancher."
你在论文里还说等到赛昂人接管地球 我在交友方面会更有运气
And your essay suggesting that I'd have better luck making friends if I wait till the Cylons take over?
请别
Please.
等等 那篇我可是认真写的
Now hold on. I put some real work into that.
是呀 可比沃尔伍兹好多了
Yes,well,it's better than what Wolowitz did.
他画了一个大阴囊的发情浣熊
He drew a raccoon with what appears to be a distended scrotum.
还真有点可爱哟
It's kinda cute.
只要不看它那玩意儿
Until you get to the scrotum.
我怎么会有希望建立新的友情关系?
What hope do I have for establishing new relationships given that
现存的朋友们都舍不得用 他们漫长生命的少许小时来帮助我
my current friends apparently could not take a few hours out of their lives to help me?
谢尔顿 我没打算为大蛋蛋浣熊说话
Sheldon,I'm not going to defend a big-balled raccoon.
我看不出你能做到
Well,I don't see how you could.
我想说的是 或许你不能把 这些当作纯粹智力习题来对待
What I'm trying to say is that maybe you can't approach this as a purely intellectual exercise.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
还记得你怎么在网上学游泳吗?
Well,remember when you tried to learn how to swim using the Internet?
我是学过游泳
Ididlearn how to swim.
在地板上学的
On the floor.
技巧是相通的
The skills are transferable.
我只是不想到水里去
I just have no interest in going in the water.
那你为啥要学游泳呀?
Then why learn how to swim?
冰盖在融化呀 莱纳德
The ice caps are melting,Leonard.
未来 游泳是不可避免的
In the future,swimming isn't going to be optional.
但你给了我灵感
But you do bring up an interesting point.
我用不着做新的研究
I don't have to break new ground here.
肯定很多研究结果是现存的
I'm sure much of the research already exists.
不 不 我想说的是 如果你想学如何交友
No,no,my point is,if you want to learn how to make friends,
到咖啡店或者博物馆去
then just go out to a coffee shop or a museum.
认识些人 和他们交流
Meet people. Talk to them.
了解下人家的生活
Take an interest intheirlives.
疯了呗
That's insane on the face of it.
- 走吧 - 我们去哪儿?
- Come on. - Where are we going?
你载我去卖场
You're driving me to the mall.
我要去买本现存交友领域的理论大全
I'm going to acquire a book that summarizes the current theories in the field of friend-making.
你干嘛不直接躺地上 游过去呢?
Why don't you just lie down on the floor and swim there?
Coping with the Death of a Loved One.
- 节哀顺变 - 感谢你
- My condolences. - Thank you.
- 家人还是朋友? - 家人
- Family or friend? - Family.
太遗憾了
Too bad.
如果是朋友 我刚好可以填补空缺
If it had been a friend,I'm available to fill the void.
没关系 她满身卫生球味道
It's just as well. She smelled like mothballs.
好吧 要是你在这嗅人玩 我去买点热脆饼
Okay,if you're gonna start sniffing people,I'm gonna go get a hot pretzel.
劳驾
Excuse me.
有交友的书吗?
Do you have any books about making friends?
嗯 有 但都是写给小孩子的
Um,yeah,but they're all for little kids.
我想技巧可以推断 道理相通嘛
I assume the skills can be extrapolated and transferred.
可能吧 就在木火车那边
I guess. They're right over there by the wooden train set.
我爱火车
I love trains.
你当然喜欢了
I bet you do.
哎 呀 还真粘
Oh,my,that's awfully sticky.
好了 我来瞧瞧哈...
All right,let's see...
Bernie Bunny Has Two Daddies Now.
估计是同志兔子的故事
That's probably about homosexual rabbits.
Gerry the Gerbil and the Bullies on the Bus.
读过了 没啥用
Read it. Not helpful.
哦 有了
Oh,here we go.
Stu the Cockatoo Is New at the Zoo.
莎拉·卡朋特作 现与其爱人 朋友马克以及鹦鹉斯图
"Author Sarah Carpenter lives in Fort Wayne,Indiana
居住于印第安纳州 韦恩堡
"with her husband and best friend,Mark,and their cockatoo Stu."
没有点交友专家的样子 你说是吧?
Hardly makes her an expert in making friends,wouldn't you agree?
我不喜欢鸟类 它们多吓人
I don't like birds. They scare me.
我也是诶
Me,too.
很多人都意识不到
Most people don't see it.
你读啥呢?
What are you reading?
Curious George.
哦 猴子我可喜欢
Oh,I do like monkeys.
好奇乔治就是猴子
Curious George is a monkey.
算是人格化的 但没错
Somewhat anthropomorphized,but yes.
或许 啥时候咱俩去看个猴子呗 你觉得好不?
Say,maybe sometime you and I could go see monkeys together. Would you like that?
好哇
Okay.
谢尔顿 你干嘛呢?
Sheldon,what are you doing?
我和这小女孩交朋友呢 你叫什么名字?
I'm making friends with this little girl. What's your name?
瑞贝卡
Rebecca.
嗨 瑞贝卡 我是你的新朋友谢尔顿
Hi,Rebecca. I'm your new friend,Sheldon.
不 别搞了 走吧
No,you're not. Let's go.
- 我俩聊得正投机呢 - 别抬头 上面有摄像头
- We were really hitting it off. - Don't look up. There's cameras.
我想知道哈 在"你有多了解谢尔顿"那项
********the "How well do you know Sheldon" section,
他最喜欢的氨基酸 你们填的啥?
what did you put for his favorite amino acid?
- 赖氨酸 - 赖氨酸
- Lysine. - Lysine.
完了 我本来写了赖氨酸 又改了
Damn it,I had lysine and changed it.
太好了 时间刚刚好
Oh,good,you're just in time.
我想我解开了交友解题步骤
I believe I've isolated the algorithm for making friends.
谢尔顿 交友哪有解题步骤啊
Sheldon,there is no algorithm for making friends.
得了 听他讲完 要是真有啥发现
Well,hear him out. If he's really onto something,
咱就在动漫大会上弄个展台 赚他一笔
we could open a booth at Comic-Con.Make a fortune.
是这样 我最初和Kripke搭话就跟
See,my initial approach to Kripke had the same deficiencies
鹦鹉斯图刚到公园时一样有着缺陷
as those that plagued Stu the Cockatoo when he was new at the zoo.
鹦鹉斯图?
Stu the Cockatoo?
没错 他是动物园新成员
Yes. He's new at the zoo.
超赞的书
It's a terrific book.
我摘录它的精华制作了流程图来指导我
I've distilled its essence into a simple flow chart that will guide me through the process.
有没有考虑过出门时把他装进大木箱里?
Have you thought about putting him in a crate while you're out of the apartment?
你好 Kripke? 我是谢尔顿·库珀
Hello,Kripke? Sheldon Cooper here.
我想到哈 你没回我的电话
It occurred to me that you hadn't returned any of my calls
是因为我没为发展友情提出实际建议
because I hadn't offered any concrete suggestions for pursuing our friendship.
或许咱俩该一起吃个饭
Perhaps the two of us might share a meal together.
了解
I see.
那有没有时间喝个热饮?
Well,then perhaps you'd have time for a hot beverage?
最受欢迎的有茶 咖啡 可可
Popular choices include tea,coffee,cocoa.
了解了解 别 先别挂
I see. No,no,no,wait. Don't hang up yet.
那娱乐娱乐怎么样呢?
What about a recreational activity?
我们肯定有共同爱好
I bet we share some common interests.
说说你有啥兴趣爱好
Tell me an interest of yours.
真的呀? 骑真马?
Really? On actual horses?
再说个兴趣爱好
Tell me another interest of yours.
抱歉 不到逼不得已 我才不下水游泳
I'm sorry. I have no desire to get in the water till I absolutely have to.
再说个兴趣爱好
Tell me another interest of yours.
哦这问题要无限循环下去了
Uh-oh,he's stuck in an infinite loop.
我来搞定
I can fix it.
有意思 但口技不是个人娱乐项目吗?
Interesting,but isn't ventriloquism by definition a solo activity?
再说个兴趣爱好
Yeah. Tell me another interest of yours.
你喜不喜欢猴子呀?
Is there any chance you like monkeys?
你咋回事嘛? 人人都喜欢猴子
What is wrong with you? Everybody likes monkeys.
别挂 Kripke
Hang on,Kripke.
没办法时 选择不太讨厌的项目
A loop counter and an escape to the least objectionable activity.
霍华德 聪明啊
Howard,that's brilliant.
你居然想到了
I'm surprised you saw that.
天呀 谢尔顿咋交不到朋友呢?
Gee,why can't Sheldon make friends?
好了 Kripke 你刚说那兴趣爱好 是我不太讨厌的
All right,Kripke,that last interest strikes me as the least objectionable,
我提议咱一起去玩
and I would like to propose that we do that together.
明天
Tomorrow.
是的 我付钱 好的 拜拜
Yes,I'll pay. All right,good-bye.
好啦 该学学攀岩了
All right. Time to learn rock climbing.
要知道 我超喜欢口技哟
You know,I am a fan of ventriloquism.
要不你我还有你的小假人去喝个热饮
Maybe you,me and your dummy could go get a hot beverage.
你喝时他表演
He could talk while you drink.
不鸟 我想攀岩
Nope. I wanna climb some rocks.
这家伙比在电脑上看起来大啊
This appears significantly more monolithic than it did on my laptop.
想看原始人怎么用骨头当武器呢
One expects to see hominids learning to use bones as weapons.
你恐高啊 库珀?
You afraid of heights,Cooper?
哪能啊 恐高完全不合理
Hardly. A fear of heights is illogical.
然而害怕掉下来 才是有发展眼光的说法
A fear of falling,on the other hand,is prudent and evolutionary.
你说要巩固我们的友情 我最少要爬多高呀?
What would you say is the minimum altitude I need to achieve to cement our newfound friendship?
好啦 这开生日会呢 小盆友都爬
Come on,they have birthday parties here. Little kids climb this.
小原始人吧
Little kid hominids perhaps.
你工作就干这点事啊? 父母一定很骄傲哈
So is this your entire job? Your parents must be so proud.
- 来啊 库珀 - 来了 Kripke
- Let's go,Cooper. - I'm coming,Kripke.
好的 绳子貌似很结实
Okay,the harness seems to be secure.
刚才有点不能自制 但网上说那是正常情况
A small amount of incontinence just now,but the Web site said that's to be expected.
也不咋难嘛 像是垂直游泳
this isn't so bad. It's like vertical swimming.
嘿 瞧瞧 库珀 都爬到一半了
Hey,look at you,Cooper. You're almost halfway to the top.
是吗?
I am?
我错了 我恐高
I was wrong. It is a fear of heights.
你还好吗 库珀?
You all right there,Cooper?
不太好
Not really.
感觉像是反正切曲线接近渐近线了
I feel somewhat like an inverse tangent function that's approached an asymptote.
你是说你卡住了?
Are you saying you're stuck?
反正切曲线接近渐近线 哪个字你不明白啊?
What part of inverse tangent function approaching an asymptote did you not understand?
我都明白 我又不是白痴 接着爬啦
I understood all of it. I'm not a moron. Just keep going.
我想我做不到
Yeah,I don't think I can.
那就爬下去
Well,then climb back down.
不行 更没可能了
No,that doesn't seem any more likely.
你打算咋办 库珀?
What's your plan,Cooper?
不能算是啥打算 我想我要晕菜了
Well,it's not exactly a plan,but I think I'm going to pass out.
抱歉 咱再做一次行吗?
I'm sorry,can we please just do it one more time?
好的 一二 一二三
Okay. One,two,one,two,three,and...
小事一件 但真是怀念啊
It's a little thing,but you really do miss it.
大家好
Hello,everyone.
我带新朋友贝瑞·克里帕奇回家吃饭了
I brought my new friend Barry Kripke home for dinner.
你们也好啊
Hello to you,too.
攀岩怎样?
How was rock climbing?
他晕过去了
He passed out.
跟个意大利腊肠一样吊在那
Just hung there like a big salami.
那 那 那是我的座
Tha-tha-that's where I sit.
你还有固定座位呢? 咋这么怪捏
Ooh,you have a special spot? What kind of wacko are you?
看你有多少时间
How much time you got?
来点中餐?
You want some Chinese food?
太好了 有牙线没?
Terrific. Got any dental floss?
在洗手间
In the bathroom.
马上回来
Be right back.
吃中餐前要先把牙里的印度菜弄出来
I got to floss the Indian food out of my teeth if I'm gonna eat Chinese.
谢尔顿 还好吗?
Sheldon,are you okay?
哦 好呀 全晕过去了 但值了
Oh,yes,I pass out all the time,but it was worth it.
我和Kripke的友情有了质的进展 但这也产生了一个尴尬的问题
I've made substantial progress in bonding with Kripke,which brings me to an awkward moment.
咋了?
What's that?
维持五个朋友的友情太困难了 所以...
Maintaing five friendships promises to be a Herculean task,so...
我要开除你们其中一个
I'm going to have to let one of you go.
我 我 选我吧
Me,me,let it be me.
莱纳德 你是我的室友 我的出行工具
Leonard,you are my roommate,my source of transportation,
床单烘干后你会为我叠好
and you help me fold my sheets when they come out of the dryer.
你安全了
You are safe.
- 能吹口哨不? - 别犯傻
- Can I whistle? - Don't be silly.
霍华德 你没有博士学位 你的古龙水刺激感官
Howard,you do not have a PhD; your cologne is an assault on the senses;
犹太重大节日期间 你不能参与电子游戏
and you're not available for video games during the Jewish high holidays.
我有罪啊 我淘汰了
Guilty as charged. I'm out.
不 你也安全
No. You too are safe.
哦 不是吧 我该怎么做呀?
Oh,come on. What do I have to do?
好了 我知道怎么个意思了
Okay,you know what? I see where this is going.
我不属于你们中的一员 我也不是科学家 直接告诉我...
I'm not one of you guys. I'm not a scientist,so just tell me...
佩妮 佩妮 佩妮 你说的都对 但请听我说完
Penny,Penny,Penny,everything you're saying is true,but please allow me to continue.
拉吉 你被淘汰了
Raj,you're out.
问的好
That's a good question.
你的确为这个同类的小团体 注入了异域的文化
While you do provide a certain cultural diversity to an otherwise homogenous group,
但你问卷的回答太闹心了
your responses to the questionnaire were truly disturbing.
你怎么会觉得我最喜欢的氨基酸是谷氨酰胺?
How could you for a moment think that my favorite amino acid is glutamine?
他写了赖氨酸 又改了
He had lysine,but changed it.
早干啥了 拉吉
Shoulda,woulda,coulda,Raj.
我喜欢在吃东西前打牙线 以便牙缝迎接新的食物
I like to floss before I eat so my gum pockets are open for new food.
你好啊!
Hello!
我以前怎会没注意到你?
How did I walk past you?
- 我是贝瑞 - 佩妮
- I'm Barry. - Penny.
呃 这名字不咋性感嘛
Eh,that's not a very hot name.
我要叫你罗姗
I'm going to call you Roxanne.
哦 饺子
Ooh,pot stickers.
突然前 我变得如此优质了哈?
Suddenly,I'm looking pretty good,huh?
Kripke 我在想你能不能借我用用 开放科学网格计算机呢?
So,Kripke,I was wondering if there's any chance you could get me some time on the open science grid computer?
- 不行 - 不行? 我们是朋友啊
- No. - No? But we're friends.
抱歉 不行 我的盆友
I'm sorry. No,my friend.
搞不懂了
I'm confused.
我以为你会让朋友用那机器的
I was given to understand that you allow your friends time on the machine.
不 不是那么回事 有正式安排的 我做不了主
No,that's wrong. There's an official schedule. I have no control over it.
看来整个尝试都是徒劳了
Well,this entire endeavor seems to have been an exercise in futility.
拉吉 你可以回来了
Raj,you're back in.
他喜欢猴子
He likes monkeys.
我得表扬他的坚持精神
*****im credit for sticking with it.
我看他是没那细胞
I didn't think he had it in him.
这次差点就到顶了啊
And he almost made it to the top this time.